A Guide to the Virginia Department of Treasury, Division of Unclaimed Property, 1822-1991
Library of Virginia
- Accession 42943,1822-1978., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 25-34)
  - Lot 955459 - Personal Papers of Mahlon Mohr,1941-1954. (1 of 3) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Lot 955459 - Personal Papers of Mahlon Mohr,1941-1954. (2 of 3) (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Lot 955459 - Personal Papers of Mahlon Mohr,1941-1954. (3 of 3) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Lot 959507 - Personal Papers of Horace K. Dickson,1925-1935. (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Lot 959507 - Personal Papers of Horace K. Dickson,1925-1935. (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Lot 963369 - Personal Papers of Wilbur G. Stevens,1962. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Lot 963847 - Personal Papers of the Keller Family,1889-1901. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Lot 970798 - Personal Papers of Alma Coles,1952-1968. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Lot 975274 - Personal Papers of Alice V. Chamblin,1943-1953. (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Lot 975274 - Personal Papers of Alice V. Chamblin,1943-1953. (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Lot 984708 - Personal Papers of Octavia L. Timberlake,1953-1959. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Lot 986182 - Personal Papers of Mr. and Mrs. John L. Walker Jr.,1956. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Lot 1018478 - Personal Papers of Swift G. Nelms Jr.,1950. (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Lot 1018478 - Personal Papers of Swift G. Nelms Jr.,1950. (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Lot 1028864 - Personal Papers of W. S. Matthews,1912-1914. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Lot 1047038 - Personal Papers of H. B. Calwell,1918. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Lot 1051605 - Personal Papers of Harry R. Eakin,1881-1955. (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Lot 1061843 - Personal Papers of Margaret C. Nuss,1940-1942. (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Lot 1068741 - Personal Papers of Harry J. Tighe,1915-1918. (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Lot 1070947 - Personal Papers of John Paul Hudson,1949-1957. (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Lot 1094953 - Personal Papers of Otto A. Isdell,1937-1950. (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Lot 1094953 - Personal Papers of Otto A. Isdell,1937-1950. (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Lot 1098287 - Personal Papers of Joseph R. Owens,1914-1926. (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Lot 1098287 - Personal Papers of Joseph R. Owens,1914-1926. (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Lot 1109228 - Personal Papers of William E. Critcher,1920. (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Lot 1109361 - Personal Papers of Dewey W. Kallam,1946-1957. (1 of 6) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Lot 1109361 - Personal Papers of Dewey W. Kallam,1946-1957. (2 of 6) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Lot 1109361 - Personal Papers of Dewey W. Kallam,1946-1957. (3 of 6) (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Lot 1109361 - Personal Papers of Dewey W. Kallam,1946-1957. (4 of 6) (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Lot 1109361 - Personal Papers of Dewey W. Kallam,1946-1957. (5 of 6) (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Lot 1109361 - Personal Papers of Dewey W. Kallam,1946-1957. (6 of 6) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Lot 1110964 - Personal Papers of Richard Carr,1957. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Lot 1123734 - Personal Papers of Robert H. Anderson,1958-1960. (1 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Lot 1123734 - Personal Papers of Robert H. Anderson,1958-1960. (2 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Lot 1131190 - Personal Papers of Stephen T. Kelsey, Jr.,1941. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Lot 1163895 - Personal Papers of Elijah Norton,1947. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Lot 1167429 - Personal Papers of Thomas L. Williams,1914. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Lot 1173389 - Personal Papers of John J. DeCarteret, Sr.,1890-1905. (1 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Lot 1173389 - Personal Papers of John J. DeCarteret, Sr.,1890-1905. (2 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Lot 1173389 - Personal Papers of John J. DeCarteret, Sr.,1890-1905. (3 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Lot 1179455 - Personal Papers of Jerry W. Hodge,1972. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Lot 1190372 - Personal Papers of Leon T. Hochstein,1954. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Lot 1200384 - Personal Papers of Brenda S. Henshaw,1959. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Lot 1207559 - Personal Papers of George C. White,1927. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Lot 1226931 - Personal Papers of Hampton Sullivan,1968. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Lot 1237512 - Personal Papers of William W. Pearsall,1967. (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Lot 1294560 - Personal Papers of Betty Crockett,1968. (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Lot 1250228 - Personal Papers of Morris Gross,1911-1924. (1 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Lot 1250228 - Personal Papers of Morris Gross,1911-1924. (2 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Lot 1251141 - Personal Papers of Margaret Grooms,1951. (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Lot 1264341 - Personal Papers of Everett H. Mosby, Jr.,1952-1966. (1 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Lot 1264341 - Personal Papers of Everett H. Mosby, Jr.,1952-1966. (2 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Lot 1264341 - Personal Papers of Everett H. Mosby, Jr.,1952-1966. (3 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Lot 1289241 - Personal Papers of the Perry Family,1951-1953. (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Lot 1300101 - Personal Papers of Curtis H. Everett Jr,1958-1960. (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Lot 1301247 - Personal Papers of N. Jennie Hare,1869-1925. (1 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Lot 1301247 - Personal Papers of N. Jennie Hare,1869-1925. (2 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Lot 1302488 - Personal Papers of Rose A. Browne,1944. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Lot 1307499 - Personal Papers of E. P. DeShazo,1908-1919. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Lot 1309907 - Personal Papers of Louise Renshaw,1953-1957. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Lot 1343914 - Personal Papers of Aralee J. Bolling,1970. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Lot 1349715 - Personal Papers of George W. Bradley, Jr.,1962. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Lot 1354494 - Personal Papers of Dennis Wayne Edmonds,1918-1967. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Lot 1357574 - Personal Papers of Roland L. Harris,1969. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Lot 1364160 - Personal Papers of Chester Robert Zemany,1965. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Lot 1377064 - Personal Papers of Conrad S. Geier, Jr,1958. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Lot 1380336 - Personal Papers of Edward G. Welch,1914. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Lot 1387812 - Personal Papers of Charles M. Stringer,1971. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Lot 1395737 - Personal Papers of Patrick J. Hogan,1946-1948. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Lot 1403159 - Personal Papers of Mary Chandler Robertson,1926-1928. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Lot 1403467 - Personal Papers of Richard Addington,1906-1912. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Lot 1417109 - Personal Papers of Mary McGeorge Collins,1967. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Lot 2936576 - Personal Papers of Ward Delaney,1961. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Lot 2936660 - Personal Papers of Ward Delaney,1961. (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Lot 2936577 - Personal Papers of the Barnett Family,1964. (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Lot 2936578 - Personal Papers of W. E. Butt,1944-1945. (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Lot 4973099 - Personal Papers of Albert Lewis,1942-1945. (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Lot 4973100 - Personal Papers of James S. Farish,1912. (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Lot 4973140 - Personal Papers of Marsha Carlan,1967-1968. (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Lot 4973140 - Personal Papers of Marsha Carlan,1967-1968. (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Lot 4973525 - Personal Papers of D. E. Lamb,ca. 1945. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Lot 4973526 - Personal Papers of Mrs. T. H. Johns,1864-1919. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Lot 4973528 - Personal Papers of Helen L. Hardy,1942-1945. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Lot 4973755 - Personal Papers of William W. Moorefield,1965-1970. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Lot 4973756 - Personal Papers of Bertha Williams,1955. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Lot 497 - Personal Papers of Eng Yick Yu,1948. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Lot 4977950 - Personal Papers of Vaughan B. Connelly,1950. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Unnumbered lot - Personal Papers of Joseph Young, Jr,1822-1917. (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Unnumbered lot - Personal Papers of Joseph Young, Jr,1822-1917. (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Accession 43250,1860-1983., Extent: 12 boxes. (Box 35-46)
  - Lot 7203 - Papers of Susie A. Williams,1929-1966. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Lot 8977 - Papers of James C. Hunt,1972-1974. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Lot 9528 - Papers of Kathi Lewis,1970-1973. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Lot 25317 - Papers of Nancy Barrow,1961. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Lot 43538 - Papers of Walter H. Hanbury,1957-1959. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Lot 47890 - Papers of Catherine C. Lee,1972. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Lot 52741 - Papers of William R. Corbin,1970. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Lot 56118 - Papers of Larry A. Anderson,1977-1978. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Lot 71657 - Papers of Clayton W. Kemp,1977. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Lot 88678 - Papers of Elma G. Firth,1971-1973. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Lot 92559 - Papers of Patricia A. Severs,1952-1977. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Lot 102029 - Papers of Katharine A. Harrison,1932-1975. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Lot 103236 - Papers of Petra G. Davis,1942-1974. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Lot 104677 - Papers of Oscar Jones,1959. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Lot 112805 - Papers of Jimmie R. Hairston,1968-1969. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Lot 1185218 - Papers of Colonia Burnette,1937-1955. (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Lot 129747 - Papers of Leroy Winfield,1980. (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Lot 130541 - Papers of Josephine J. Bailey,1964-1966. (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Lot 130780 - Papers of Muriel Maddle and Joyce Coffen,1963-1976. (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Lot 131446 - Papers of Louis Campanelli,1973. (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Lot 132027 - Papers of William Baylor,1967-1972. (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Lot 133698 - Papers of Jerry L. Hales,1970. (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Lot 134958 - Papers of James T. Gemmill,1932-1972. (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Lot 135517 - Papers of Jon M. Maxwell,1965. (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Lot 137103 - Papers of Larry T. Spicer,1953-1982. (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Lot 137103 - Papers of Larry T. Spicer,1953-1982. (2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Lot 139163 - Papers of Christiana D. Malcolm,1959. (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Lot 143760 - Papers of Dorothy W. Horne,1949-1966. (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Lot 144991 - Papers of Randolph C. Foster,1973. (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Lot 115952 - Papers of Verlie S. Pitts,1971. (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Lot 166085 - Papers of Ruth Ann Bailey,1929-1972. (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Lot 183689 - Papers of David Manning, Jr.,1973-1976. (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Lot 183689 - Papers of David Manning, Jr.,1973-1976. (2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Lot 187602 - Papers of Mary Anne Nofflet,1947-1975. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Lot 200468 - Papers of Man Yuen Cheung,1974-1975. (1 of 3) (Box 36)
  - Lot 200468 - Papers of Man Yuen Cheung,1974-1975. (2 of 3) (Box 36)
  - Lot 200468 - Papers of Man Yuen Cheung,1974-1975. (3 of 3) (Box 36)
  - Lot 200959 - Papers of James F. Peterson,1972. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Lot 205851 - Papers of John F. Manley,1971-1972. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Lot 223289 - Papers of Ann Saady,1933-1958. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Lot 227790 - Papers of Sarah Ore,1931-1972. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Lot 229081 - Papers of Curtis A. Hoback,1916-1974. (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Lot 229081 - Papers of Curtis A. Hoback,1916-1974. (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Lot 23246 - Papers of George M. Van Besien,1968. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Lot 235660 - Papers of Richard G. Newman,1957. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Lot 250220 - Papers of Lucy F. Spencer,1924-1958. (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Lot 252538 - Papers of Rhea A. Underhill,1973. (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Lot 260776 - Papers of Decie I. and Robert Byrnes,1961-1963. (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Lot 262129 - Papers of Clarence E. Kunkel,1976. (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Lot 262507 - Papers of Patricia A. Kenney,1963-1969. (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Lot 267910 - Papers of Robert Durbin,1963-1965. (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Lot 275121 - Papers of Nita Johnson,1923-1968. (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Lot 277320 - Papers of Edna R. Bland,1969. (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Lot 280024 - Papers of Romeo M. Mitchell,1951-1973. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Lot 281756 - Papers of Joseph Schwerin,1932-1968. (1 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Lot 281756 - Papers of Joseph Schwerin,1932-1968. (2 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Lot 281756 - Papers of Joseph Schwerin,1932-1968. (3 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Lot 281756 - Papers of Joseph Schwerin,1932-1968. (4 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Lot 282545 - Papers of James R. Cooke,1977. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Lot 284623 - Papers of Warren Taylor Jr,1972. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Lot 294974 - Papers of Norton M. Bowman Jr,1980. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Lot 299850 - Papers of Floyd A. Rogers,1939-1974. (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Lot 299850 - Papers of Floyd A. Rogers,1939-1974. (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Lot 306979 - Papers of Curtis C. Summey,1975-1976. (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Lot 309952 - Papers of Carl R. Knutson,1922-1950. (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Lot 309952 - Papers of Carl R. Knutson,1922-1950. (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Lot 311075 - Papers of William A. Igel,1971-1976. (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Lot 312408 - Papers of Papers of John E. Eagle,1919-1963. See also oversized Box 46. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Lot 322979 - Papers of Norman Cohen,1944-1971. (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Lot 322979 - Papers of Norman Cohen,1944-1971. (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Lot 344612 - Papers of John W. Day,1954. (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Lot 345736 - Papers of Raymond D. Royall,1957-1964. (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Lot 356306 - Papers of Lydia Mae Wright,1899-1975. (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Lot 356306 - Papers of Lydia Mae Wright,1899-1975. (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Lot 362886 - Papers of Mary S. Komoroski,1946-1964. (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Lot 368961 - Papers of Patricia A. Campbell,1963-1978. (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Lot 368961 - Papers of Patricia A. Campbell,1963-1978. (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Lot 383110 - Papers of Thelma Richard,1958-1976. (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Lot 384931 - Papers of Robert J. Keen,1979. (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Lot 390224 - Papers of Lucille G. Baker,1937-1950. (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Lot 390224 - Papers of Lucille G. Baker,1937-1950. (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Lot 393122 - Papers of William H. Murray, Jr.,1947-1981. (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Lot 393122 - Papers of William H. Murray, Jr.,1947-1981. (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Lot 393590 - Papers of Leonard Tucker,1941-1973. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Lot 398549 - Papers of Russell S. Dunnavant, Jr,1958-1965. (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Lot 398549 - Papers of Russell S. Dunnavant, Jr,1958-1965. (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Lot 404146 - Papers of William W. Barkely,1971. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Lot 405624 - Papers of Sheila Darling,1979. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Lot 411238 - Papers of John C. K. Shipp,1957-1973. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Lot 415424 - Papers of Clyde M. Denton,1961-1962. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Lot 424221 - Papers of Mary S. Harris,1968-1970. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Lot 426285 - Papers of Matthew T. Sutich,1948-1970. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Lot 427675 - Papers of James R. Trent,1956-1961. (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Lot 427675 - Papers of James R. Trent,1956-1961. (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Lot 428490 - Papers of Judy E. Young,1974. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Lot 455392 - Papers of Francine L. Kelly,1860-1937. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Lot 456562 - Papers of Debra T. Spence,1974. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Lot 460202 - Papers of Robert Lege,1953. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Lot 458680 - Papers of Dorothy A. Koehler,1972. (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Lot 462803 - Papers of Wanda Jones,1978-1980. (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Lot 468943 - Papers of Ralph W. Smith,1952-1972. (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Lot 471401 - Papers of Annie M. Evans,1976. (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Lot 477010 - Papers of Dennis L. Higgs,1973-1977. (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Lot 477406 - Papers of Jerry Venable,1973-1977. (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Lot 485519 - Papers of Donald Elkins,1964-1972. (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Lot 487721 - Papers of Budd C. Moyer, Jr.,1971-1973. (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Lot 502507 - Papers of Grace M. Wideman,1953-1968. (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Lot 507396 - Papers of Abe G. Handler,1945-1972. (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Lot 508240 - Papers of William H. Donison,1953-1964. (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Lot 521474 - Papers of William D. Baumgardner,1970-1976. (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Lot 521474 - Papers of William D. Baumgardner,1970-1976. (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Lot 523860 - Papers of Arthur E. Hostetter,1941-1962. (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Lot 527157 - Papers of Frank Mullen,1965. (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Lot 537620 - Papers of James W. Parham,1970-1971. (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Lot 542408 - Papers of Philps Machinery and Tractor, Inc.,1974. (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Lot 555654 - Papers of Anne Byrd,1982. (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Lot 557736 - Papers of Lawrence R. Barger,. (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Lot 565807 - Papers of Annemarie Clindedinst,1913-1973. (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Lot 565807 - Papers of Annemarie Clindedinst,1913-1973. (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Lot 568360 - Papers of Stanley C. Daniel, Jr.,1889-1975. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Lot 569779 - Papers of Joann Johnson,1942-1980. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Lot 571698 - Papers of Deborah A. and Michael J. Veitch,1969-1972. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Lot 577730 - Papers of Betty S. and Newell H. Grant, Jr.,1975. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Lot 581539 - Papers of Stanley Williams,1940-1978. (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Lot 581539 - Papers of Stanley Williams,1940-1978. (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Lot 582125 - Papers of Edward C. Larson,1949-1971. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Lot 582125 - Papers of Robert E. Riley,1971-1974. (1 of 3) (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Lot 582125 - Papers of Robert E. Riley,1971-1974. (2 of 3) (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Lot 582125 - Papers of Robert E. Riley,1971-1974. (3 of 3) (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Lot 585136 - Papers of James Ailor,1948-1971. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Lot 587868 - Papers of Jerome A. Trawbridge,1974. (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Lot 590130 - Papers of Strauss and Budnick,1968-1975. (1 of 8) (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Lot 590130 - Papers of Strauss and Budnick,1968-1975. (2 of 8) (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Lot 590130 - Papers of Strauss and Budnick,1968-1975. (3 of 8) (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Lot 590130 - Papers of Strauss and Budnick,1968-1975. (4 of 8) (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Lot 590130 - Papers of Strauss and Budnick,1968-1975. (5 of 8) (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Lot 590130 - Papers of Strauss and Budnick,1968-1975. (6 of 8) (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Lot 590130 - Papers of Strauss and Budnick,1968-1975. (7 of 8) (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Lot 590130 - Papers of Strauss and Budnick,1968-1975. (8 of 8) (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Lot 610716 - Papers of Bobby G. Hicks,1975. (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Lot 611952 - Papers of Loren A. Clark,1946-1977. (1 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Lot 611952 - Papers of Loren A. Clark,1946-1977. (2 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Lot 611952 - Papers of Loren A. Clark,1946-1977. (3 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Lot 612536 - Papers of Jasper Lee Godwin,1966-1969. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Lot 622240 - Papers of Joseph F. Slaughter,1957-1958. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Lot 640712 - Papers of Kyn S. Sharpley,1969. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Lot 660259 - Papers of Thomas A. Hill,1972. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Lot 663377 - Papers of Henry A. Kiser,1976. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Lot 667081 - Papers of Jason A. Smith,1980. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Lot 669514 - Papers of Frances M. Tarcen,1958-1977. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Lot 571259 - Papers of Betty W. Olson,1971. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Lot 676887 - Papers of Harry M. Fry,1941-1974. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Lot 678682 - Papers of Kenneth A. Lehman,1967-1969. (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Lot 680011 - Papers of Leon Goodman, Jr.,1966. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Lot 683261 - Papers of Moses M. Wilkins,1947-1953. (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Lot 690862 - Papers of Robert M. Stoverink,1969-1972. (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Lot 693773 - Papers of Constance M. Watson,1963. (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Lot 694767 - Papers of Jack R. Kallmyer,1972. (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Lot 695369 - Papers of Jesse Featherston,1977. (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Lot 696520 - Papers of Jung Gwang Kim,1982-1985. (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Lot 701119 - Papers of Harold Hanson III,1976. (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Lot 709809 - Papers of James F. Haag,1973-1976. (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Lot 716406 - Papers of A. W. Garrett,1969. (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Lot 723156 - Papers of Nancy A. Benton,1948-1980. (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Lot 732644 - Papers of Sherwood McKinney,1967-1970. (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Lot 750872 - Papers of Robert H. Underwood,1963. (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Lot 761336 - Papers of John, Betty, and Katherine Weber,1948-1978. (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Lot 765706 - Papers of Judy V. Knight,1947. (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Lot 768978 - Papers of Montise L. Lewis,1972-1973. (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Lot 771348 - Papers of William R. Greco,1968-1969. (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Lot 771897 - Papers of Ollie Gay and Charles Goode,1958-1965. (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Lot 778966 - Papers of Terrie L. Cole,1950-1977. (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Lot 780111 - Papers of Ruby C. Goodnow,1959-1975. (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Lot 781208 - Papers of Joseph Schwerin,1863-1971. (1 of 5) (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Lot 781208 - Papers of Joseph Schwerin,1863-1971. (2 of 5) (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Lot 781208 - Papers of Joseph Schwerin,1863-1971. (3 of 5) (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Lot 781208 - Papers of Joseph Schwerin,1863-1971. (4 of 5) (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Lot 781208 - Papers of Joseph Schwerin,1863-1971. (5 of 5) (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Lot 783317 - Papers of Robert Nichols and John Russell,1936-1979. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Lot 786676 - Papers of Judith B. Allen,1936-1979. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Lot 790904 - Papers of Ellen B. Arrington,1971. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Lot 791258 - Papers of Herbert Mills,1946. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Lot 801762 - Papers of Joseph C. Finegan,1942-1952. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Lot 802606 - Papers of Clarence E. Harper,1965. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Lot 805703 - Papers of Joyce V. Williams,1958-1967. (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Lot 805703 - Papers of Joyce V. Williams,1958-1967. (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Lot 807314 - Papers of Presley M. Wilkes,1956-1959. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Lot 812893 - Papers of Norman W. Cohen,1975-1981. (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Lot 812893 - Papers of Norman W. Cohen,1975-1981. (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Lot 815454 - Papers of David M. Ashbolt,1966. (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Lot 817294 - Papers of Roger Vaughn,1966-1975. (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Lot 822917 - Papers of Stanton S. Nickens,1974. (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Lot 818066 - Papers of Martha West and Rita W. Poindexter,1945-1962. (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Lot 822252 - Papers of William Fitzsimmons,1976. (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Lot 824334 - Papers of Barden B. Grimes,1915-1961. (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Lot 824689 - Papers of Susan Sutherland,1974-1976. (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Lot 824807 - Papers of Eleanor Vaughan,1940-1968. (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Lot 826758 - Papers of Davis R. McRae,1975-1976. (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Lot 833008 - Papers of Norma Smallwood,1978. (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Lot 837635 - Papers of Frederick S. Fuhrman,1976. (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Lot 841281 - Papers of William Halloway,1939-1950. (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Lot 842449 - Papers of Joyce R. Wise,1974. (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Lot 844129 - Papers of Ernest R. Clendenon,1915. (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Lot 855493 - Papers of John N. Federspiel,1973. (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Lot 859959 - Papers of Allen J. Lagerman,1945-1975. (1 of 3) (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Lot 859959 - Papers of Allen J. Lagerman,1945-1975. (2 of 3) (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Lot 859959 - Papers of Allen J. Lagerman,1945-1975. (3 of 3) (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Lot 865739 - Papers of Richard Proffitt III,1962-1967. (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Lot 868928 - Papers of Dan McAllister,1976-1979. (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Lot 868928 - Papers of Dan McAllister,1976-1979. (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 32)